const SAMPLE_FLASHCARDS = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "FTP",
    answer: "Port 20 and 21",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "SSH",
    answer: "Port 22",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "SFTP",
    answer: "Port 22",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Telnet",
    answer: "Port 23",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "SMTP",
    answer: "Port 25",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "DNS",
    answer: "Port 53",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "DHCP",
    answer: "Port 67 and 68",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "TFTP",
    answer: "Port 69",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "HTTP",
    answer: "Port 80",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "POP3",
    answer: "Port 110",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "NTP",
    answer: "Port 123",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "NetBIOS",
    answer: "Port 139",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "IMAP",
    answer: "Port 143",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "SNMP",
    answer: "Port 161 and 162",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "LDAP",
    answer: "Port 389",
  },
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "HTTPS",
    answer: "Port 443",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "SMB",
    answer: "Port 445",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Syslog",
    answer: "Port 514",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "SMTP TLS",
    answer: "Port 587",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "LDAPS",
    answer: "Port 636",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "IMAP SSL",
    answer: "Port 993",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "POP3 SSL",
    answer: "Port 995",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "SQL",
    answer: "Port 1433",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "SQLnet",
    answer: "Port 1521",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "MySQL",
    answer: "Port 3306",
  },
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "RDP",
    answer: "Port 3389",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "SIP",
    answer: "Port 5060 and 5061",
  },
];

export default SAMPLE_FLASHCARDS;
